仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.ZiMuZu.tv
原创翻译  双语字幕
翻译:  亲爱的小饭   小笼包
翻译:  吃货丁小七  ET外星人
校对:  慕容龙飞
时间轴:  浓子
后期:  瓜瓜2016版    总监： 瓜瓜
打开微信   扫描左侧二维码
或搜索公众号:    美剧炸了
了解最新影视资讯字幕信息
摩  登
家  庭
第七季 第十六集
最新美剧下载
www.ZiMuZu.tv
谢谢
Thank you.
有试喝
Samples!
打扰一下  我认识你吗
Excuse me, do I know you?
恐怕不吧
I don't think so.
你好面熟  我怎么想到了长椅上的广告
You look so familiar. Why am I picturing a bench ad?
小有名气  不得不承认了
Minor celebrity. Guilty as charged.
你是牙医广告上那个人
You're the "Accidentes" guy.
不  不  不
No. No, no, no.
我是...
Um, I'm, uh...
我是房地产先生  菲尔·邓菲
I'm Mr. Real Estate -- Phil Dunphy.
对
Oh, right.
其实我最近正在找房子
I am actually looking for a house right now.
如果我能帮得上忙的话
Well, if I could be of any service...
我没  我手头没有名片
I don't -- I don't have any cards.
我穿的是去健身房的衣服
I'm in my gym clothes.
看来那杯热巧克力是锻炼后的奖赏啦
Oh, I see you earned that hot chocolate.
是啊  我刚刚进行了一次
Yeah, I rocked a pretty intense
高强度摇哑铃快步走
Shake Weights/Power Walk Combo.
早上好  邻居们
Morning, neighbors.
我昨天看到了你女儿  家有小女初长成
Saw your daughter yesterday. Boy, she is growing up fast.
我叫安吉
My name is Angie.
这是我的号码
Here is my number.
如果你在这附近有看到什么三卧室的房子
If you find any good three-bedrooms in the neighborhood,
可以介绍我看看
I'd love to see them.
我会给你打电话的  很愿意带你看房
Well, I'll call you. I'd love to show them to you.
我可不只有一张让人们坐的帅脸[板凳广告]
I'm not just a pretty face people sit on.
当作没听见吧
Forget...I said that.
来了
Here you go.
谢谢  亲爱的
Oh, thanks, honey.
安吉是谁
Who's Angie?
我刚在里面见到的一个女的
Just a woman I m-met inside.
是吗  她还给你她的号码了
Really? She gave you her number?
还把"i"上的点画成了小爱心
And dotted her "i" with a little heart?
对啦  她在找房子
Oh, yeah. She's looking for a house.
温柔的老女人
Sweet old lady.
我不知道我为什么那么说
Don't know why I said that.
有点胖
Little overweight.
不知道我怎么想的
No idea where that came from.
非常重的爱尔兰口音
Thick Irish accent.
我慌神了
I panicked!
我应该说实话的
I should have told the truth,
但是克莱尔知道我  有个喜欢的类型
but Claire knows I have... a type.
那只是个善意[白人]的谎言
It was just a little white lie.
很讽刺吧
Ironically.
你好  美国
Hey, America!
我没看到你们来了
I didn't see you there.
欢迎来到全新的网络直播节目"杰说心语"
Welcome to another live webcast of "Jay Talking."
杰说心语
杰·普里契特
你们知道我很讨厌什么吗
You know what really gets my goat?
山羊奶酪
Goat cheese.
到处都有
It's on everything.
我讨厌死了
I hate it.
唯一比山羊奶酪更讨厌的是
The only thing worse than goat cheese
跟一些在室内戴帽子的傻瓜
is eating it at a communal table
一起在公共场合吃那玩意儿
with some jerk wearing a hat inside.
放尊重点
Have some respect.
把裤子拉上去
And pull up your pants!
有些胖子裤子提不上去  弯腰的时候屁股缝会漏出来
我唯一想看到的裂纹是独立钟上的那条
Only crack I want to see is in the Liberty Bell.
地球上最棒的国家
Greatest country on the damn planet.
如果六个月前
If, six months ago,
你告诉我我会办一个很厉害的网络节目
you'd have told me I'd have a big Internet show,
我会说那挺合理的
I would have said, "Yeah, that adds up."
我以前常常用笑话和评论逗乐我的员工们
I used to entertain my staff with jokes and observations.
我退休后
When I retired,
我开始也在这家里这么干
I started sharing those gems around the house.
结果曼尼太喜欢了  于是建了个网络直播站
Manny went so nuts for it, he set up the whole webcast.
抱歉  互联网  把锅甩给你们了
Sorry, Internet. He's your problem now.
你们一天圈这人圈那人倒还不那么招人厌
Bottom line, you can keep your hashtags,
因为我喜欢炸薯饼[谐音]
'cause I like hashbrowns.
但是...
But, hey...
那只是"杰说心语"
that's just "Jay Talking."
结束了
And we're out.
90分钟时间飞逝
90 minutes just flew by.
各位
Hey, guys!
评论已经进来了
The comments are already rolling in!
"继续下去  杰"
"Keep it up, Jay."
"你说的正是我们想的"
"You're saying what we're all thinking."
"我也好想念炒杂碎[美式中菜]"
"I miss Chop Suey, too."
我爱死了
I love it,
因为大家都会看到我天天要忍受什么了
because now everybody gets to see what I live with.
什么情况  又是这个家伙
What the hell? This guy again?
谁
Who?
一个名叫"女士杀手52"的傻瓜
Some meatball named "LadyKiller52"
已经连续骚扰我好几天了
been dogging me for days.
看看他写了什么
Look what he wrote.
“老头  没人管你想什么"
"Hey, Grandpa, no one cares what you think."
你确定那不是海莉说的吗
Are you sure that that's not from Haley?
这还有一条  还是那个傻瓜发的
Here's another one. The same jerk!
"真奇怪你居然不喜欢山羊奶酪"
"It's weird you don't like goat cheese
"你长得就像山羊啊"
when you've got a goat face."
这说不通啊
Well, that makes no sense.
什么山羊会吃自己的奶酪啊
What kind of goat eats its own cheese?
我来这里  想为美国人带来欢笑  引发思考
Here I am, trying to make America laugh and think,
结果这个傻瓜老是跑来骂我
and this hockey puck's coming at me with tired insults.
好吧  他就是在故意煽动  杰
Okay, I-it's called a troll, Jay.
但你不能让他或者任何什么事情
But you can't let him or anything else
阻止你把你的所有想法
keep you from directing all of your opinions
都传到电脑里
into that computer.
没错  曼尼
You're right, Manny.
做公众人物确实不容易
It's tough being in the public eye.
总算知道辛纳特拉[美国歌手]为什么老打人了
Now I know why Sinatra was always punching guys.
好啊  克莱尔
Hola, Claire.
怎么了
What's going on?
你经常做瑜伽对吧
You do a lot of yoga, right?
以前啦
Ah, I used to.
但是跟那些扎着马尾
But all those judgy vegans
穿着紧身裤的圣母严格素食主义者在一起
with their ponytails and their Lululemon,
我觉得自己土鳖还是待在家里算了  你懂吧
I'm like, "Nama-stay home," You know what I mean?
我刚开始学
I just started taking it,
但我觉得那个教练喜欢上我了
but I think that the instructor is hitting on me.
-没错  -你怎么知道
- He is. - How do you know?
因为你穿着瑜伽裤[很紧绷]呢
Because you're you in yoga pants.
换个课上吧
Just go to another class.
但是这课真的很好
But this one is perfect.
正好跟乔去上金宝贝同一时间
It's at the same time as Joe's Gymboree,
又在隔壁
right next door.
要不你跟我一起去
Ay, why don't you come with me today
然后告诉我是不是我想太多了
and tell me if I'm just being crazy?
行啊  把具体信息发给我
Sure. Text me the info.
提醒她
Hey, remind her!
别忘了
And don't forget --
今天有全新一集的"杰说心语"哦
today, all-new episode of "Jay Talking".
他要聊聊那些
He takes on restaurants
把菜单写在黑板上的饭馆
that write their menus on blackboards.
我想要菜单在我手里的感觉
I want to feel a menu in my hands!
姐们
Hey, girl.
-你要干什么  -没什么
- What are you doing? - Nothing.
就是想跟你打个招呼  聊点事情
Just wanted to say hi, talk about stuff.
什么事情
What stuff?
我不知道  我只是想你了
I don't know. I just miss you.
什么都可以聊啊
We could talk about anything.
聊聊  水门事件怎么样
How about... Watergate?
比如  你觉得
Like, what would you say
改变美国政治最重要的
were the three most significant ways
三个方面是什么
it changed American politics?
把引文也说一下
Cite your sources.
我不会帮你写论文的
I'm not writing your essay.
好吧  复活节见
Okay. See you at Easter.
我回来了
I'm back.
带"小心心"安吉看房看得怎么样了
How'd your showing with Angie-with-a-heart go?
还好吧  都挺正常的
Oh, fine. Uneventful.
乏善可陈
Nondescript.
这个淋浴房好小啊
This shower's really small.
你能想象我用这浴室吗
Could you imagine me in here?
非常奇怪  我跟她在一起待了两个小时
Weird thing -- I was with her for two hours,
放在人群里我还是认不出她
I couldn't pick her out of a crowd.
真的吗  太奇怪了
Really? That is weird.
没什么奇怪的啊
Nothing weird about it.
你刚刚说那很奇怪
You just said it was weird.
那确实很奇怪  亲一个
That's weird. Give me a kiss!
你在干什么呢  兄弟
What are you up to, buddy?
写一篇关于尼克松总统的论文
Writing a paper on President Nixon.
好傻啊
What an idiot.
他拥有了一切  又因为一些愚蠢的谎言
He had it all and just threw it away
失去了这一切
because of some stupid lie.
也许他说出口之前
Well, maybe it came out of his mouth
都不知道自己在说什么
before he knew what he was saying.
然后他的谎越撒越多
Okay, but then he just kept lying over and over
接着要用更多的谎去圆
and making it worse and worse.
菲尔  安吉多大
Phil, how old is Angie?
70岁  怎么了
Oh, uh, gosh... 70. Why?
我在想福赛斯街那套房子
I was thinking about that house on Forsyth.
挺不错的  就是楼梯多了点
It's nice but has a lot of stairs.
不  她太胖了没法住
No. She's too... fat for that.
因此  我将从今天中午起
Therefore, I shall resign the presidency
辞去总统职务
effective at noon tomorrow.
他要是说实话就好了
If only he had told the truth.
他陷得太深了
He was in too deep!
看看我买了什么
Check out what I got!
不用了  谢谢
No, thanks.
我们明天可以去公园
Thought we could go to the park tomorrow
这样你就可以开始尝试学了
and you could finally learn.
尝尝水泥地的味道吗
What pavement tastes like?
我不想去
I don't think so.
莉莉  等你准备好了随时可以用
Well, Lily, when you're ready, it's here for you.
米奇尔  我们能去卧室
Mitchell, can I, um, speak to you in the bedroom
聊聊床罩的事吗
about the, uh, dust ruffle?
别担心  "床罩"现在就走
Don't worry -- the dust ruffle's leaving.
你干嘛这么做
Okay, why are you doing this?
我们得让莉莉学会骑车
We need Lily to get on this bike.
你为什么那么逼她这么紧
Why are you pushing this so hard?
很明显她害怕
She's clearly afraid.
她最近怕很多事
She's been afraid of a lot of things lately.
上周  她连衣橱门都不开
Last week, she wouldn't even open her closet door
因为她觉得里面有可怕的东西
because she thought something scary was in there.
可能是你妈给她做的牛仔连身裤
Could be the denim jumpsuit your mom made her.
这是个关键时刻
This is a pivotal moment.
我们的孩子绝不能
We can't raise a child
连车都不会骑  或者害怕上飞机
who won't ride a bike or get on an airplane
或者不吃蛋黄酱
or eat mayonnaise.
跟口感有关  鸡蛋怎么会变成那个样子
It's a texture thing. How does egg become that?
明天学定了  她一定要骑上这部车
We are doing this tomorrow. She is getting on this bike.
你急什么啊  她才八岁
What's the rush? She's 8 years old.
大部分她同龄的越南孩子都骑着单车去工作了
Most Vietnamese kids her age are already riding a bike to work.
圣雄之手在哪
So, where's Mahatma Handsy?
我知道你很会玩瑜伽方面的双关语
I noticed that you have a lot of these yoga puns.
我觉得我们不需要用那些
I don't think we need any more.
合十礼
Namaste.
好吧  他还是老样子
Okay. Now I get the one from before.
我们没见过吧
We haven't met.
克莱尔
Claire.
你真美
Beautiful.
就像唐君鲁的日出一般
Like the sunrise in Tanjung Rhu.
你身材很适合练瑜伽  以前练过吗
You have a great yoga body. You've done this before?
挺久以前了  不过我是练过
Um, yeah. I mean, it's been a little while, but yeah.
姿势很棒  很有力量
Great posture, strong core.
你会享受一番的
We're going to have fun.
也许我最近压力有点大  不过我错了
Maybe I've just been stressed lately, but I was wrong.
瑜伽很有意思
Yoga felt good.
把臀部撅向天花板
We are lifting our hips towards the ceiling.
很棒  克莱尔
Very nice, Claire.
拉很擅长指导
Ra was very supportive.
也许是我以前没找对教练
Maybe I just never had the right teacher.
我做对了吗
Am I doing it right?
而且还能免费停车
And they validate parking.
又来了一条
Another one?
我受够了这个叫女士杀手的混蛋
I've had it with this LadyKiller son of a bitch.
他一整晚都在骂我的视频
He's been lobbing insults all night.
"蠢货  我能透过网络闻到你的呼吸"
"Hey, dumbbell, I can smell your breath through the Internet."
这应该不可能吧
They can't do that, right?
杰  听听我这个局外人的意见
Jay, take it from a fellow performer --
如果你决定成为公众人物
If you're going to put yourself out there,
那就要做好面对负面评论的
you need to let the criticism roll off your back.
说真的  我蛮惊讶的  你居然没有因为
I must say, I was impressed you didn't mope for a month
对你《音乐之声》上表现的恶评抑郁一整个月
after that brutal review of you in "Sound of Music".
你说什么呢  哪有评论啊
What are you talking about? There was no review.
那周学校没有校报
There was no school paper that week.
就是啊  那周没有校报
Eeeeeexactly. There was no paper that week.
对啊
Oh, yeah.
你做了什么
What did you do?
我
I...
我不会傻站在这里
I am not going to stand here
让你把校报被偷的错都怪在我身上
and let you accuse me of stealing all of those papers!
他没那么说
He didn't say that.
"看过曼尼·迪尔加多"
"After seeing Manny Delgado
"演崩了的冯特拉普上校"
mangle the role of Captain Von Trapp,
"我只想说  上帝啊  让他停下吧"
all I can say is "Doe-a-dear Lord, make it stop.
"搞得我年纪轻轻就得开始吃抗抑郁药了"
I am 16 going on antidepressants.
"我想爬上所有山峰然后跳下来"
I wanted to climb every mountain and jump off."
什么老师会允许这种文章
What teacher allowed this?
爷爷好
Hey, Grandpa.
亲爱的
Hi, honey!
真高兴你打电话过来
Oh, I'm so glad you called.
我这周真是太糟糕了
I've just been having the worst week.
我压力太大了
It's been so overwhelming and so much --
你知道该怎么办吗  喝杯鸡尾酒
You know what helps? A cocktail.
听着  我现在有个问题
Listen, I've got a situation.
你认识能够在网上
Do you know any computer nerds
查到人家身份的电脑死宅吗
that can track someone down on the Internet?
我应该认识一些
Yeah, I think I can find a few.
好了  很激动吧  莉莉
Okay! How exciting is this, Lily?
马上你就能学会骑单车了
In no time at all, you're gonna be a bike rider.
或者变成一具尸体
Or a corpse. Okay...
我知道你害怕  要是你能够说出
I know you're afraid, and sometimes it's helpful
自己究竟怕什么  会更有帮助
if you say exactly what you're afraid of out loud.
所以呢
So...?
我害怕自己会摔倒
I'm afraid I'll fall
因为我还没准备好而你一直逼我
because I'm not ready and you forced me,
我下半辈子都会记着这仇了
so for the rest of my life, I'll hold it against you.
而在其他时间
And then other times,
还是应该克服困难坚持去学
it's just best to tamp it down and soldier on.
你把她从车上拽出来的时候我就说过了
I said this when you pried her out of the car,
我再说一遍  她不想学
and I'll say this again -- she doesn't want to do this!
她看到这有多简单就会想学了
She will when she sees how easy it is for me.
看吧  小菜一碟
See? Easy as pie!
莉莉  如果你不想学
Okay, look, Lily, if you don't want to do this --
-我不想学  -好吧
- I don't want to do this. - Okay.
我没事
I'm good!
听着  我会去跟爸爸说
Um... look. All right. I'm gonna talk to Daddy.
不过答应我你总有一天会学的
But just promise me you'll learn someday, okay?
还有你会去坐飞机
And that you'll get on a plane.
我为什么会不想上飞机  什么情况
Why wouldn't I get on a plane? What's wrong with them?
没事  飞机比车安全
Nothing. They're safer than cars.
车不安全吗  天哪
Cars aren't safe?! Oh, my God.
大爸来了
Okay! Look -- here's Daddy.
我平安地回来了
Here we are, safe and sound!
-发生什么事了  -没什么
- What's wrong? -Nothing.
我想到吃完早餐以后忘了关烤箱
I just think I left the oven on at home after breakfast,
我们得走了
so we should get going.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
你早上吃的是麦片
No, you had cereal for breakfast.
发生什么事了
What's going on?
我摔了一跤  好像把胳膊摔折了
I wiped out, and I think I broke my arm.
我从来没这么疼过
I've never been in so much pain.
保持微笑
Keep smiling.
得送你去急诊室
Got to get you to an ER.
不  不要  不要
No, don't! No, no!
莉莉要是看到我受伤肯定不会想学骑车的
If Lily sees me hurt, she's never gonna get on a bike.
你摔是因为那个慢跑的裸男吧
You crashed because of that shirtless jogger, didn't you?
天啊  他是有够性感
Oh, my God. Right?
歌洛莉亚  我刚还在想你今天会不会来
Oh, Gloria! I was wondering if you were gonna be here today.
你来干什么
What are you doing here?
我得说  我还以为我已经厌倦瑜伽了
I got to say, I thought I was over yoga,
可是昨天真是让我大开眼界
but yesterday was a real eye-opener.
大开"眼界"还是"腿界"啊
"Eye" or "Thigh"?
我觉得这个课很有挑战性
I thought it was a very challenging class,
还有我不太喜欢你暗示的东西
and I don't really appreciate anything else you're implying,
因为你有点...
'cause you're a little...
我怎么了
I'm what?
嫉妒
Jealous.
嫉妒什么  嫉妒他蹭你吗
Of what? Of him rubbing you
蹭得好像要把灯灵放出来了吗
like he was expecting a genie to come out?
你一直都习惯成为男性的关注焦点
Look, you are so used to being the center of men's attention
昨天你可能有点不开心  因为我也得到了
that yesterday, it probably bothered you that I... got some.
关注  仅此而已  仅仅是关注
Attention. That's all. Just attention.
你疯了吗  我都结婚了
That's insane. I am a married woman.
我一直都得不到什么关注
I am used to getting no attention.
不  安吉  你离我只有一个转角
No, Angie, you're like right around the corner from me.
对  向左转  朝西走
Yeah, turn left, walk west,
我们美发沙龙门口见
and I'll see you in front of the hair salon.
好的  待会儿见
All right. See you in a minute.
菲尔
Phil?
不要啊
No!
你们准备干什么去
What are you guys up to?
我要上瑜伽课
I have a yoga class.
很明显  克莱尔也要一起去
And, apparently, Claire does, too.
你在这里干嘛
What are you doing here?
正准备带我的胖爱尔兰客户
Oh, just on my way to show more houses
安吉·整容婆去看房子
to my fat, Irish client, Angie O'Plasty.
我要进去了
I'm going in.
我会告诉拉你到了
I will tell Ra that you're here.
拉是我们的瑜伽教练
Ra is our yoga instructor.
她肯定很厉害  你都连续两天来这儿了
Oh, she must be great. You're here two days in a row.
她是挺厉害的
She is great.
就是年纪有点大
She's a little old.
真不清楚我为啥那么说
Don't know why I said that.
我得进去了
I got to go.
回[黑]家见
See you black home.
非常清楚我为什么那么说
Pretty sure I know why I said that.
这是我人生中最大的伤痛
This is the most pain I've ever been in in my life.
况且我曾经还被马一脚踢到电铁丝网上呢
And a horse once kicked me into an electric fence.
好了小卡  你的胳膊断了
Well, C-Cam, yeah, you broke your arm.
你得去医院
You got to go to the hospital.
不  不着急
No. Not yet.
我先进房  泡个澡
I'll go in, draw myself a bath,
然后假装滑倒把胳膊给摔断了
pretend to fall and break my arm.
与此同时  你把你扭伤脚的时候
In the meantime, go get those painkillers
用的止痛药拿来
that they gave you when you twisted your ankle.
我好像已经扔了
Oh, I think I threw those away.
真的吗
Did you?
还是你把它们放在你枕边的床头柜上了
Or are they in the nightstand next to your bed
因为它们是很好的红酒伴侣
because they go good with a glass of wine?
大爸
Dad?
怎么了
Yeah?
你能把这个打开吗
Can you open these?
当然可以了
'Course I can.
好  那你开吧
Well? Will you?
可以呀  现在就要开吗
Uh...sure. Yeah. Now?
试试看
Let's see here.
那啥
Ooh, you know what?
要开这个其实有个很好玩的办法
There's a fun way to open these
不知道我有没有教过你
I don't know if I've ever taught you.
搞定  我的妈呀
There! Whoopsie-daisy!
祝你吃得开心  洗澡时间到
Bon appetit. Bath time!
好了  我拿来了
Okay, so, I got the --
这是怎么回事
What happened here?
大爸开的薯片
Daddy opened the chips.
用什么开的  吹雪机吗
With what -- a snowblower?
那是什么声音呢
Oh, I wonder what that noise was.
真希望大爸没事
I hope Daddy's okay!
-大爸  -噢  不
- Daddy! - Oh, no!
你看上去好像滑倒了  摔断了左手臂
Looks like you fell and broke your, uh, left arm.
不  米奇尔  我摔了  真心摔了
No, Mitchell, I fell. I really fell.
-这是真的吗  -真的
- Oh, really? - Really.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
头好痛  手臂也好痛
My head hurts. And my arm.
我再也不要洗澡了
I'm never taking a bath again!
这下好了
Oh, great.
你没从钢管上掉下来真是不幸
Too bad you didn't fall off a stripper pole.
对不起
I-I'm sorry.
那是左手臂  在左手边
That is the left. Left.
艾丽克斯找的电脑宅给我的地址就是这儿
Well, this is the address Alex's nerds gave me,
但我觉得这不像是挑衅鬼住的地方
but it's not where I pictured a troll living.
"自从主演《音乐之声》"
"After his performance in 'The Sound of Music,'"
"克里斯托弗·普卢默走上了杰出演员之路"
"Christopher Plummer went on to a distinguished acting career."
"而自从看了迪尔加多的表演  我认为"
After Delgado's performance, I expect he'll go on
"他可以走上杰出水管工[谐音普卢默]之路"
"to a distinguished plumbing career."
专心点  你得给我明天的节目拍好这段
Focus! I need you to film this for my show tomorrow.
还有如果这个废物未成年  就得靠你揍他了
By the way, if the punk's under 18, you have to hit him.
美国传统教育允许用拳头解决问题  但要自己承担责任  同时未成年人不打比自己小的  成年人不打未成年人
什么  我可没同意这点
What?! I never agreed to that!
普里契特
Pritchett?
厄尔
Earl?
杰的前合作伙伴  "衣柜衣柜衣柜"公司老板
你是在逗我吧
You've got to be kidding me.
你来这里干什么
What the hell are you doing here?
我来打女士杀手的肥脸
I'm here to punch LadyKiller in his fat face.
抱歉能再来一遍吗  我调的是拍照模式
I'm sorry. Can we start over? I was on "Photo."
继续吧  我准备好了
Go ahead. Any time.
你真可悲
You're pathetic.
我在衣柜生意上狠狠打败了你
I crushed you in the closet game,
我也要在互联网上打败你
and I'm crushing it on the Internet.
把那耗子放下  我要把你打趴在门口
Put that rat down, and I'll crush you on your porch.
这样也比不上你的没脑乱叫让人痛苦
Like that is gonna be any more painful than your stupid rant,
"餐厅什么时候变得这么吵了"
"When did restaurants get so loud?"
我早该知道是你
I should have known it was you --
你的短胖小手指打了那么多错字
all those typos from your stubby fingers.
怎么说话呢  我的手是像我妈
Watch it. I got my mother's hands.
你的猥琐胡子也像你妈
You also have your mother's mustache.
-拿着  -帮我拿着
- Hold this! - Hold this.
整整撕了二十秒
That went on for a good 20 seconds.
我们干嘛要一直互撕
Why do we keep doing this?!
谁知道呢
Who knows?
你们还看不出来吗
Isn't it obvious?
你们两个彼此需要  这就是原因
You two need each other. It's what drives you.
这孩子说得对
The kid is right.
我起床有一半原因是为了战胜你
Beating you is half the reason I get out of bed.
纠缠不休的角斗
Locking horns.
我们促使彼此变得更好
We made each other better
比我想象的还要好
than I ever thought we could be.
把对方推到了伟大的高度上
Pushed each other to greatness.
不能更高
We touched the sky.
但是我们说的是衣柜生意  对吧
We're talking about closets here, right?
抱歉  你是在说那个
Oh, I'm sorry -- You mean the sanctuary
让男人早晨得以充分武装
where a man dons his armor in the morning
夜晚总结回顾一天战斗的圣所吗
and takes stock of the battle at night?!
我们所有人拥有的一个共同点
The one thing we all have in common --
不管是总统还是邮递员  大亨还是教师
presidents to postmen, tycoons to teachers,
穿越四海
from sea to shining sea!
这剧情转变得也太诡异了
This is taking a weird turn.
我们的确让彼此展现出了最好的一面
We did kind of bring out the best in each other,
不是吗
didn't we?
你干嘛非得退休呢  普里契特
Why did you have to retire, Pritchett?
我想念我们之间的火花
I miss the fire.
我猜我也无法割舍
I guess I miss it, too.
好吧  我想说
All right, here's something.
我们一起拍视频秀怎么样
What if we do the show together?
什么  不要
What? No!
我才不会让你盯上我的新晋热门秀呢
I'm not gonna let you glom onto my new hit show!
阅读量只有43
43 views.
我们可以做一期观点对立的那种节目
We could do like a -- like a point/counterpoint kind of thing.
比如说我提出一个观点  像...
Like I would say something like, uh...
"废弃美分吧"  然后你的观点是
"Let's get rid of pennies," And you would say...
我们当然该弃用美分
Of course we should get rid of pennies!
美分用起来太烦了
They're annoying to own
要真扔了它们你又会不乐意
and make you feel bad when you throw them out.
好吧  那我就说"怀念送奶工"
All right, what -- what if I said "I miss milkmen"?
谁不怀念呢
Who doesn't miss milkmen?
那牛奶瓶  那小领结
The glass bottle, little bow tie.
我是傻子吗  我会不怀念送奶工
What am I, an idiot? I don't miss milkmen?
行  那你来出主意
Okay, well, then you think of something!
我可不是被试镜的那个
I'm not the one auditioning.
好吧
Okay.
我想到一个代表我独特思维的点子
Here's something that represents my unique brand of thinking.
我坐飞机的时候  觉得行李费收得好
When I fly, I like luggage fees.
我也是
Me too.
我们这些随身携带行李的人凭什么
Why should us carry-on folk have to foot the bill
要替不懂打包行李的笨蛋承担费用呢
for those morons who don't know how to pack?!
整整三个星期  我从爱丁堡飞到华沙
Three weeks, I went from Edinburgh to Warsaw
只穿两条裤子戴一顶苏格兰宽顶无沿圆帽
on two pairs of pants and a tam-o'-shanter.
我快睡着了
I'm falling asleep.
-我喜欢打个小盹  -谁不是呢
- I love naps! - Who doesn't?
这太可笑了
This is ridiculous!
你觉得可笑是不是因为尽管你们是死敌
The irony that, despite you two being mortal enemies,
但其实你们对任何事情的看法都一致
it appears you agree on everything?
才不是
No!
是因为这个混蛋竟然以为
It's that this jackass thinks
他真能为《杰说心语》带来新创意
he can actually bring something new to "Jay Talking."
拜托  我们会超神的
Come on! We would be magic!
你已经从我这儿偷走了一家公司
You already stole one company from me.
你这次休想再得逞
You're not getting this.
行  好
Okay, fine!
我要自己弄个节目
I will start my own show.
名字就叫《厄尔智言》
I'll call it... "Earls of Wisdom."
我等不及看了
Can't wait.
评论区见
I'll see you in the comments section.
我会关闭评论功能
I'll just turn the comments off.
-这能实现吗  -能啊
- You can do that? - Yeah.
那我来这里搞什么
Then why am I here?!
你真的不用这么做
Really, you don't have to do this.
如果我不送你来拿钥匙
If I don't drive you to get your keys,
你要怎么开车呢
how are you gonna get your car?
谢谢
Well, thank you.
那就是我家
This is me right here.
不是这里  不是这里  后两间
Not here. Not here. Two down.
我突然有点胃绞痛
Oh, there's a stomach cramp.
好多了  就是那里
Much better. Uh, right here.
邮箱地址"珀特菲尔德"[运输工原野]这家吗
With the mailbox that says "Porterfields"?
是的  这是我们跟邮差开的玩笑  说来话长
Yep. It is a joke that we play with the mailman. Long story.
我很快回来
I will be right back.
喂
Hello?
克莱尔  我是拉
Hey, Claire? It's Ra.
来电显示是"伊拉·巴恩博"
The readout said "Ira Burnbaum".
是的  "拉"是"伊拉"的简称
Yeah. Uh, "Ra" is short for "Ira."
我在想你要不要一起出来
Anyway, I was wondering if you wanted to get together,
洗个澡看个电影什么的
maybe grab a shower and a movie?
不  不
No. No.
我...
Oh, I am...
伊拉  我结婚了  这是不可能的
Ira, I'm a married woman. That's not gonna happen.
我趴在你身上的时候没感受出来
I didn't pick up that energy when I was planking you.
菲尔  你在家做什么
Phil! What are you doing home?
我丢了车钥匙  你在跟谁讲电话
I lost my car keys. Who were you talking to?
-没有谁  为什么你裤子破了 -没有为什么
- Nobody. Why are your pants ripped? - No reason.
找到了  待会见
Here they are. See you later!
你在这
There you are.
我们走吧
Off we go.
Phil  为什么你没让我看这幢房子
Phil, why didn't you show me this house?
它满足我所有的需求
It has everything I want.
我忘了它在待售了
I forgot it was for sale.
你可是中介
You're the agent.
我记起来了  它建得不好
I remember -- It's built cheap.
我觉得挺结实的
It...looks pretty solid to me.
空有其表而已
Well, it's mostly held up by beehives.
走吧
Let's go.
菲尔  到底怎么了
Phil, what is going on?
没什么  只是不想让你住在次品房子里
Nothing. Just trying to keep you away from all that asbestos.
你不想让我当你的邻居吗
Do you not want me as a neighbor?
好吧
Okay.
我坚持不下去了  实话实说吧
I-I can't do this anymore. No more lies.
跟这有关
It is related to that.
我还真不知道你是个种族主义者
I did not peg you for a racist.
等等  不  不  不  不
Wait. No, no, no, no, no!
等等  等等  安吉
Wait, wait, wait. Angie...
世事总是那么难料
It's always the last people you think.
我们结束了  再见  菲尔
We're done. Goodbye, Phil.
不  安吉  不是这样的
No, Angie! That's not it!
我对我妻子撒了谎
I lied to my wife
因为她知道我对黑人有幻想
because she knows I have a thing for black women!
是吗
Oh, really?
嘿
Hey, there!
所以那就是安吉吗
So, that was Angie O'Hara?
好吧
Okay.
我向你坦白
Full disclosure...
我确实说谎了
I did lie.
但只是因为她很漂亮  而你又有点神经质
But only because she's beautiful and you get a little crazy.
我到底是为什么要这么说
Why the hell did I say that?!
对不起
I'm sorry.
没关系
Oh, it's okay.
你现在那么善解人意  太不像你了
You're being so understanding. It's so unlike you.
你是不是不为人知地疯了
Are you secretly mad?
你是不是在给我安全的错觉
Are you lulling me into a false sense of security?
你是不是要在我睡着的时候对我做什么
Are you gonna do something to me while I'm asleep?
菲尔  你知道真正让我生气的是什么吗
Phil, you know what really gets my goat?
是你说谎了
That you lied.
看来男人都这样
Guess men are men.
不知道为什么我会有奢望
I don't know why I expected anything more.
喂
Hello?
我想给你道歉  你说得对
I want to apologize. You were right.
拉只关心你确实让我生气
It did bother me that Ra gave you all the attention.
他是个有魅力的男人  而你是个非常性感的女人
He's an attractive man, and you're a very sexy woman.
他当然会四处摸你
Of course he put his hands all over you.
-什么  -是拉吗
- What? - Ra?
是菲尔
It's Phil.
再...再见
B-Bye-bye!
克莱尔...
Claire...
你知道真正让我生气的是什么吗
You know what really gets my goat?
好吧  莉莉  开始吧
Okay, Lily. Let's do this.
我们能不能先别骑了
Can we just please give this a rest
等你完全好了再说
until you're fully recovered?
不  米奇尔  我们都陷得太深了
No. Mitchell, we're in too deep.
我摔断了手臂  我还忘了
I have a broken arm, and I can't remember
任何一位小学老师的名字
any of my grade-school teachers' names.
你已经说了四次了
Yeah, you've mentioned that four times now.
-真的吗  -是的
- Have I really? - Yeah.
好吧  莉莉  上车吧
All right. Uh, Lily, let's -- let's get on the bike.
小心点  小心点
Carefully. Carefully.
一次上一条腿
One leg at a time over.
脚踏在踏板上  很好
Feet on the pedals. Perfect.
然后就开始踩踏板
And then we start pedaling.
米切尔  开始踩踏板
Mitchell, we start pedaling.
好  放手吧
Good. Now let go.
-别放手  -好
- Don't let go! - Okay.
米奇尔  放手
Mitchell, let go.
-我没准备好  -她没准备好
- I'm not ready. - She's not ready!
米切尔  过来一下
Mitchell, sidebar, please.
好的  好的  停下来
Okay. Okay. Stopping.
把脚放下来  我很快回来
Just put your feet down. Be right back.
怎么了  莉莉  你不会骑自行车吗
What's wrong, Lily? Don't you know how to ride a bike?
我会  悉尼  我只是在教他们怎么教小孩
Yeah, Sydney. I'm just showing him how to teach a kid.
我却步不前是因为我摔伤了头
Okay, I'm dragging my feet because I have a brain injury.
你又是为什么
Why are you dragging yours, again?
因为我不想让她受伤
Because I don't want her to get hurt!
她终于开始变得谨慎了
No, see, it's not the worst thing in the world
这并不是什么坏事
that she's actually starting to be cautious.
她以前从书架上飞下来  从秋千上跳下来
She used to fly off of bookcases and jump off of swing sets,
而现在她想保护自己了
and now she's trying to protect herself.
那如果她什么都害怕
And what kind of life is she gonna have
她会拥有怎样的人生呢
if she's scared of everything?
我不需要担心她的人生
A life where I don't have to worry about her.
我懂了
I get it.
所以你才是害怕的那一个
So you're the one that's afraid.
外面是危险的
It's dangerous out there.
世界上有太多奇奇怪怪的事情发生了
T-There's so much weird stuff going on in the world,
而我只是  我只想她安全
and I just... I want her to be safe.
如果她想的话  我们也可以过几周再学
I guess we can wait a couple weeks if she wants to.
莉莉  这...
Lily, it's...
莉莉
Lily?
小卡  看
Cam, look!
天啊  太好了
Oh, my gosh! That's so great!
上帝  希望如此
God, I hope so.
一切都会好的
Ohh, everything's gonna be okay.
是呀
Yeah.
特威戴尔老师  四年级
Miss Tweeddale -- fourth grade.
科里查克老师  卢根老师
Mr. Kleezak! Mr. Lundgren!
我想起来了
I'm back!
我的天  我说过...
Oh, my God. I told...
安吉  谢谢你能跟我见面
Angie, thank you so much for meeting me.
这是我的妻子  克莱尔
This is my wife, Claire.
你要知道我丈夫
You need to know that my husband
绝对不是一个种族主义者
is the furthest thing from a racist.
我爱黑人女性
I love black women.
也许有点过了
Maybe a little too much.
我跟她说你是白人
So, I told her that you were white,
也只是因为这样
which is the only reason
我才不想你住在对面
I didn't want you living across the street.
我不想让她发现我在说谎
I didn't want her to find out that I was lying.
真的吗
Is that true?
不幸的是  这是真的
Sadly, yes.
这样我就放心了
Well, I am relieved.
虽然被归为某类人还是有点无礼
Although it is a little offensive to be reduced to a type.
当然  对不起
Of course. I'm sorry.
亲爱的  一切都还好吗
Hey, babe. Everything okay?
是的  一切都还好
Uh, yeah. Everything's fine.
这只是一场很大的误会
It's just a big misunderstanding.
这是菲尔
Uh, this is Phil.
还有他的妻子  克莱尔
And his wife, Claire.
你好
Hello.
我们接受道歉
Yeah. Apology accepted.
姐这是要走向巅峰啊
I'm on fire.